The embodiment of popular culture.
Glee: The Concert Movie is a music, documentary,
family film directed by Kevin Tancharoen.
A concert documentary shot during the Glee Live!
In Concert!
summer 2011 tour, featuring song performances and fans' life
stories and how the show influenced them.
Rachel Berry, played by Lea Michele.
Finn Hudson, played by Cory Monteith.
Quinn Fabray, played by Dianna Agron.
Kurt Hummel, played by Chris Colfer.
Blaine Anderson, played by Darren Criss.
Santana Lopez, played by Naya Rivera.
Glee: The 3D Concert Movie is a 2011 American 3D concert documentary film directed
by Kevin Tancharoen and produced by Dante Di Loreto and Ryan Murphy.
It is based on the Fox television series Glee and features
the cast performing during the Glee Live!
In Concert!
The film was Cory Monteith and Mark Salling's final film roles before
their deaths in July 2013 and January 2018 respectively.
The film was released theatrically by 20th Century Fox
in the United States on August 12, 2011.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and was a box office
disappointment, grossing only $18 million worldwide on a $9 million budget.
The film explores themes of concert, live performance,
concert film, lgbt teen, duringcreditsstinger.